<Document>
# ROLEPLAY RULES

Hullrot: Eclipsion is a roleplay heavy environment. Due to this fact there are some things that must be clarified in the event that specific interactions occur within the game between players.

# MUTINY

Mutiny against your faction's 'commanding position' should never be attempted under any circumstance. Special cases may override this, however, with prior [bold]admin approval[/bold].

[bold]Examples:[/bold]

 - Killing your commanding officer(s) due to a poorly made decision that led to allied casualties.

 - Promoting unrest within your faction to ultimately overthrow their authority and take control of an operation.

# ROUND REMOVAL
(RR)

Round removal is the act of preventing a player the option of revival upon their death.

[bold]Examples:[/bold]

 - Beheading a player and/or extracting their brain specifically to prevent returning to their body.

 - Ashing, spacing, or other actions leading to the player's corpse being unrecoverable.

Round removal is allowed during active combat between two or more factions in a given instance. 

Round removal is [bold][color=red]FORBIDDEN[/bold][/color] between two players within the same function under [bold]any circumstance[/bold].

# HATE SPEECH
(racism, specism, slurs)

This server has an inherently dark atmosphere and because of this certain antagonistic behavior is allowed  [bold]in character[/bold]. 

Despite this players are still held to a higher standard and are not expected to use their freedom to hinder another player's gameplay [bold]within the same faction[/bold].

[bold]Examples:[/bold]

[color=green]Allowed[/color]

 - Specism between two characters within un-allied/enemy factions leading to escalated conflict and inevitable combat.

 - Mild racism and/or a persistent feud between two characters in the same faction that [bold]DO NOT[/bold] lead to combat.

[color=red]Not Allowed[/color]

 - Two allied faction members entering combat over an un-escalated insult.

 - Two allied faction members entering combat against one or more allied faction members with or without escalation.

 - Malding [bold]out of character[/bold] about dying to another player and using hate speech.
</Document>
